[{"answer": "My back is killing me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ex-Girlfriend.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Oh yeah, everybody's guy is the best", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "You should just do it like a Ban", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ex-Girlfriend.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Hi.", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Alright..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ex-Girlfriend.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "It's very good", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Ah, huh. It's good", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ex-Girlfriend.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Good, huh", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "It's very good", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ex-Girlfriend.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Good", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I don't return fruit. Fruit is a gamble. I know that going in.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ex-Girlfriend.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You did it? What happened", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Well, yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ex-Girlfriend.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I don't know. They're books", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Why not", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ex-Girlfriend.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Oh, no, no, no. I pay what I say. ", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "It's okay", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ex-Girlfriend.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I'm not taking it back", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Let me taste it.  See, that stinks. You can't eat that. You should take it back", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ex-Girlfriend.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Alright, I'll take it back. I'm going by there", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I don't care about it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ex-Girlfriend.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Alright. Take it back.", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Well", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ex-Girlfriend.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " Oh. Oh, my friend", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Yeah, I took her home one night", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ex-Girlfriend.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I was. She's got me, like, hypnotized", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I don't know. But I don't. I'm actually almost happy to hear it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ex-Girlfriend.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I guess I should be but I'm not", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I know, I know", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ex-Girlfriend.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "See her tonight. See her tomarrow. Go. Knock yourself out. She's too crazy for me", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "It was embarrassing to me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ex-Girlfriend.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Why don't you make a point with your own doctor?  What's wrong", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I guess I just didn't expect it from the way you've been acting", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ex-Girlfriend.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Of course I want to talk about it", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Well, to be honest, it just didn't make it for me. It's just so much fluff", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ex-Girlfriend.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I can't be with someone if I don't respect what they do", "qsentId": 36}]